<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[dereferenced[dev]]]></title><description><![CDATA[the ranting of some unknown developer]]></description><link>https://dereferenced.dev</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 21:30:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[what is the point? ideas free of authority]]></title><description><![CDATA[You don’t know who I am, and I’ve intended it to be that way. I want to have a place that I (or possibly anyone else) could express my…]]></description><link>https://dereferenced.dev/what-is-the-point/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://dereferenced.dev/what-is-the-point/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 12:12:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;You don’t know who I am, and I’ve intended it to be that way. I want to have a place that I (or possibly anyone else) could express my thoughts and opinions independent of my identity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As it turns out, its a little bit more challenging than I thought it would be to setup a blog that is unable to be directly tied to who you are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m sure that someone with a lot of skill can decipher who I am, but I at least tried to take precautions without going to the extreme of using an anonymous hosting service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I made sure that I have privacy protection on my domain provider.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I created a separate GitHub account that uses separate SSH keys (without my personal email in the comments) so that you couldn’t lookup my public keys on GitHub.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m sure I missed other things and someone will immediately point out where I went wrong and ruin this from the get-go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The efforts I made to try to make this independent of who I am known as isn’t the point. The point is that that what is shared here should stand on its own merit, not be accepted simply because of how well known I am (I’m not), where I work (inconsequential), or some other reason that you would give more credence to what is being expressed. There are a lot of really great blogs out there by really well known people, but I think that sometimes makes us want to give more weight to what they’re saying because of who they are, and not because of what they’re &lt;em&gt;saying&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a longer-winded way to say I just want to avoid any kind of appeal to authority here. Hell, if someone else wants to write something to be shared on here without having their name signed to it, I would be more than happy to (obviously subject to review). Its the whole point of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh and yeah, its mostly developer-centric with occasionally meandering on other topics. This is an experiment, so we’ll see how it goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to contribute, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:message@dereferenced.dev&quot;&gt;send it&lt;/a&gt; or just message on twitter.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>